<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>INSPIRE Lab @ UCF on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</title>
    <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in INSPIRE Lab @ UCF on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Md Nafees Fuad Rafi</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_nafees_fuad_rafi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_nafees_fuad_rafi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Md. Nafees Fuad Rafi is a Ph.D. student of Civil Engineering with a focus on Transportation Systems Engineering at the University of Central Florida. Before joining UCF, he worked as a faculty member at AUST, Dhaka, Bangladesh. He has completed his B.Sc. in Civil Engineering at Khulna University of Engineering &amp;amp; Technology (KUET), Khulna, Bangladesh. His research interest includes Travel Behavior Modeling, Smart Mobility, Data Analytics etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MohamadReza GhorbanaliZadegan</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/mohammadreza_ghorbanalizadegan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/mohammadreza_ghorbanalizadegan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MohammadReza is a PhD student in Civil Engineering (focus: Transportation Systems Engineering) at the University of Central Florida. He earned his undergraduate from Islamic Azad University and master&amp;rsquo;s from Sharif University of Technology, both in Industrial Engineering. He has a strong background in Operations Research, Mathematical Formulation, and Optimization. Mohammadreza&amp;rsquo;s research interests revolve around the application of mathematical and computational tools to address real-world problems in fields like transportation and logistics. He is currently working on the optimization of alternative fuel vehicles and their infrastructure planning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nima Rashgi Shishvan</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/nima_rashgi_shishvan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/nima_rashgi_shishvan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nima earned his undergraduate degree in Civil Engineering from the University of Tehran, followed by a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Civil Engineering with a specialization in Transportation Engineering and Planning from Sharif University of Technology. Currently, he is pursuing his doctoral studies at UCF. His primary research focuses on the utilization of information and communication technologies in transportation, as well as freight transportation and logistics, and the development of sustainable transportation systems.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saman Mazaheri Khameneh</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/saman_mazaheri_khameneh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/saman_mazaheri_khameneh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Saman is a PhD student in Civil Engineering (focus: Transportation Systems Engineering) at the University of Central Florida. She earned both her BS.c and MS.c degrees from University of Tabriz majored in Electrical Engineering. . She has a strong background in power systems, and her research interests revolve around intersection of power systems and transportation systems. She is currently working on the application of optimization tools in transporation related to electric vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSF CAREER Award</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf2023_career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf2023_career/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to receive the NSF CAREER Award this year. Especially thanks my mentors, students, and friends who have helped greatly to this achievement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The topic of my CAREER proposal is on &amp;ldquo;A Decentralized Optimization Framework for Next-Gen Transportation and Power Systems with Large-scale Transportation Electrification&amp;rdquo;, aiming to contribute to the efficiency, sustainability, and resilience of these two critical infrastructure systems leveraging electric vehicles. Look forward to broad collaboration and discussion on this topics.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSF Workshop: Cyber-enabled to Support Carbon-Neutral Electricity and Mobility</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf2023_workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf2023_workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dr. Guo will serve as the panelist on the NSF-sponsored workshop: Cyber-enabled to Support Carbon-Neutral Electricity and Mobility at TAMU from Apr. 24-25, 2023. The title of his talk is on Opportunities and Challenges for Large-scale Transportation Electrification.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System-level impacts of en-route information sharing considering adaptive routing</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/trc2023_afifah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:50:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/trc2023_afifah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-optimization of Charging Scheduling and Platooning for Long-haul Electric Freight Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/trc2022_alam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:50:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/trc2022_alam/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electric Vehicles for Distribution System Load Pickup Under Stressed Conditions: A Network Equilibrium Approach</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/tps2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:58:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/tps2022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Pricing of Ride-sourcing Services in a Congested Transportation Network</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/trc2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:50:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/trc2022/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best student paper award (Energy Systems Track, 3rd place) in IISE Annual Conference</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2022_best_student_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2022_best_student_paper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;INSPIRE LAB&amp;rsquo;s paper on Multi-stage Charging Station and Distributed Generator Planning in Decentralized Power Distribution and Transportation Systems received the 3rd place in the best student paper award competition in Energy System Track in IISE Annual Conference 2022. Congratulations Sina and Rakibul!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations at IISE 2021</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2022_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2022_talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We will have three presentations at IISE Annual Conference 2022 at Seattle from May 21 to May 24, 2022. Sina will present the work, coauthored with Rakibul Alam and Dr. Guo, on multi-stage multi-agent charging infrastructure and distributed generators planning in coupled transportation and power systems.  Dr. Guo will present two of the works on the charging infrastructure planning for ride-sourcing systems (coauthored with Rakibul) and network modeling with en-route information updates for transportation systems (coauthored with Fatima).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimization-based trip chain emulation for electrified ride-sourcing charging demand analyses</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/tl2022a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:58:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/tl2022a/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charging Infrastructure Planning for Ride-sourcing Electric Vehicles Considering Drivers’ Value of Time</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/tl2022b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:58:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/publication/tl2022b/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at 2022 7th Annual UTC Conference for the Southeastern Region</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/utc2022_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/utc2022_talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rakibul presented one of his recent research at 2022 7th Annual UTC Conference for the Southeastern Region. The title of the presentation is Co-optimization of Charging Scheduling and Platooning for Long-haul Freight Electric Vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
