<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>data-analytics on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</title>
    <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/tags/data-analytics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in data-analytics on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/tags/data-analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Md Nafees Fuad Rafi</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_nafees_fuad_rafi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_nafees_fuad_rafi/</guid>
      <description>Md. Nafees Fuad Rafi is a Ph.D. student of Civil Engineering with a focus on Transportation Systems Engineering at the University of Central Florida. Before joining UCF, he worked as a faculty member at AUST, Dhaka, Bangladesh. He has completed his B.Sc. in Civil Engineering at Khulna University of Engineering &amp;amp; Technology (KUET), Khulna, Bangladesh. His research interest includes Travel Behavior Modeling, Smart Mobility, Data Analytics etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tadeas Lobreis</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/tadeas_lobreis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/tadeas_lobreis/</guid>
      <description>Tadeas Lobreis is a senior Computer Science student at the University of Central Florida. Tadeas graduated with Associates in Arts degree for St. Petersburg College in Clearwater, Florida before transferring to UCF. He is currently working as an undergraduate researcher for Dr. Guo and completing a senior design project sponsored by Mitsubishi Motors. His interests include AI and Machine Learning, especially when pertaining to hardware applications. Tadeas hopes to continue his education with a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Data Science after graduation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>