<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>transportation electrification on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</title>
    <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/tags/transportation-electrification/</link>
    <description>Recent content in transportation electrification on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/tags/transportation-electrification/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Md Nafees Fuad Rafi</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_nafees_fuad_rafi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_nafees_fuad_rafi/</guid>
      <description>Md. Nafees Fuad Rafi is a Ph.D. student of Civil Engineering with a focus on Transportation Systems Engineering at the University of Central Florida. Before joining UCF, he worked as a faculty member at AUST, Dhaka, Bangladesh. He has completed his B.Sc. in Civil Engineering at Khulna University of Engineering &amp;amp; Technology (KUET), Khulna, Bangladesh. His research interest includes Travel Behavior Modeling, Smart Mobility, Data Analytics etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MohamadReza GhorbanaliZadegan</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/mohammadreza_ghorbanalizadegan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/mohammadreza_ghorbanalizadegan/</guid>
      <description>MohammadReza is a PhD student in Civil Engineering (focus: Transportation Systems Engineering) at the University of Central Florida. He earned his undergraduate from Islamic Azad University and master&amp;rsquo;s from Sharif University of Technology, both in Industrial Engineering. He has a strong background in Operations Research, Mathematical Formulation, and Optimization. Mohammadreza&amp;rsquo;s research interests revolve around the application of mathematical and computational tools to address real-world problems in fields like transportation and logistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saman Mazaheri Khameneh</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/saman_mazaheri_khameneh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/saman_mazaheri_khameneh/</guid>
      <description>Saman is a PhD student in Civil Engineering (focus: Transportation Systems Engineering) at the University of Central Florida. She earned both her BS.c and MS.c degrees from University of Tabriz majored in Electrical Engineering. . She has a strong background in power systems, and her research interests revolve around intersection of power systems and transportation systems. She is currently working on the application of optimization tools in transporation related to electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sina Baghali</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/sina_baghali/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/sina_baghali/</guid>
      <description>Sina got his undergraduate degree from the University of Tabriz and his master&amp;rsquo;s degree from K. N. Toosi University of Technology both majored in Electrical Engineering. Before joining UCF, his research include modeling power systems in optimization problems and modeling renewable energy resources based on data analytics. He is currently a P.h.D student at UCF working on the interdependencies of power and transportation systems in terms of resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>