<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</title>
    <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NSF CAREER Award</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf2023_career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf2023_career/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to receive the NSF CAREER Award this year. Especially thanks my mentors, students, and friends who have helped greatly to this achievement.
The topic of my CAREER proposal is on &amp;ldquo;A Decentralized Optimization Framework for Next-Gen Transportation and Power Systems with Large-scale Transportation Electrification&amp;rdquo;, aiming to contribute to the efficiency, sustainability, and resilience of these two critical infrastructure systems leveraging electric vehicles. Look forward to broad collaboration and discussion on this topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NSF Workshop: Cyber-enabled to Support Carbon-Neutral Electricity and Mobility</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf2023_workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf2023_workshop/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Guo will serve as the panelist on the NSF-sponsored workshop: Cyber-enabled to Support Carbon-Neutral Electricity and Mobility at TAMU from Apr. 24-25, 2023. The title of his talk is on Opportunities and Challenges for Large-scale Transportation Electrification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best student paper award (Energy Systems Track, 3rd place) in IISE Annual Conference</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2022_best_student_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2022_best_student_paper/</guid>
      <description>INSPIRE LAB&amp;rsquo;s paper on Multi-stage Charging Station and Distributed Generator Planning in Decentralized Power Distribution and Transportation Systems received the 3rd place in the best student paper award competition in Energy System Track in IISE Annual Conference 2022. Congratulations Sina and Rakibul!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentations at IISE 2021</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2022_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2022_talk/</guid>
      <description>We will have three presentations at IISE Annual Conference 2022 at Seattle from May 21 to May 24, 2022. Sina will present the work, coauthored with Rakibul Alam and Dr. Guo, on multi-stage multi-agent charging infrastructure and distributed generators planning in coupled transportation and power systems. Dr. Guo will present two of the works on the charging infrastructure planning for ride-sourcing systems (coauthored with Rakibul) and network modeling with en-route information updates for transportation systems (coauthored with Fatima).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at 2022 7th Annual UTC Conference for the Southeastern Region</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/utc2022_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 16:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/utc2022_talk/</guid>
      <description>Rakibul presented one of his recent research at 2022 7th Annual UTC Conference for the Southeastern Region. The title of the presentation is Co-optimization of Charging Scheduling and Platooning for Long-haul Freight Electric Vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New funded project on optimizing information value in stochastic transportation systems, sponsored by NSF.</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf_funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/nsf_funding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Poster Award (2nd place) in INFORMS Annual Conference</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2021_best_poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2021_best_poster/</guid>
      <description>INSPIRE LAB&amp;rsquo;s poster on Spatial Pricing of Ride-sourcing Services in a Congested Transportation Network received 2nd place in the poster competition in INFORMS Annual Conference 2021. Congratulations Fatima!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New funded project on Evaluating and Validating Technology Options for Estimating Transit Vehicle Occupancy in Real Time, sponsored by FDOT and collaborated with FSU and FIU</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/fdot_funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/fdot_funding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New funded project on deep reinforcement learning for speed control for network safety, sponsored by Safer-Sim Tier 1 UTC</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/safer_sim_funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/safer_sim_funding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best paper award (Energy Systems Track) in IISE Annual Conference</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2021_best_paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2021_best_paper/</guid>
      <description>INSPIRE LAB&amp;rsquo;s paper on Impacts of Privately Owned Electric Vehicles on Distribution System Resilience: A Multi-agent Optimization Approach received best paper award in Energy System Track in IISE Annual Conference 2021. Congratulations Sina!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at IISE 2021</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2021_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2021_talk/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Guo will have one presentations at IISE Annual Conference 2021 (virtual). He will present the work, coauthor with his PhD student Sina Baghali, on impact of private electric vehicles on distribution system resilience on May. 24, 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at TRB 2021</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/trb2021_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 16:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/trb2021_talk/</guid>
      <description>INSPIRE lab will present four of recent research at TRB 2021 (virtual): (1) spacitial (1) Statistical Modeling for Charging Behavior of Plug-in Delectric Vehicles using Large-Scale Charging Data; (2) A Stochastic Multi-Agent Optimization Framework for Interdependent Transportation and Power System Analyses; (3) Energy Impact Analyses of Electrified Ride-Sourcing Services without Trip-Chain Data; (4) Spatial Pricing of Ride-sourcing Services in a Congested Transportation Network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at INFORMS 2020</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2020_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 16:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2020_talk/</guid>
      <description>INSPIRE lab will present two of recent research at INFORMs 2020 (virtual): (1) EV charging behavior study using large-scale supply-side charging data. (2) A Stochastic Multi-Agent Optimization Framework for Interdependent Transportation and Power System Analyses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New funded project on assessing societal understanding of existing/future vehicle technologies, sponsored by Safer-Sim Tier 1 UTC and AAA Foundation for Traffic Safety.</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/aaa_fts_funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/aaa_fts_funding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at INFORMS 2019</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2019_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2019_talk/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Guo will present two of his work on renewable generator planning and EV charging incentive design considering transportationa and power interdependency at INFORMs 2019 in Seattle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New publication</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/tse2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/tse2019/</guid>
      <description>New publication in value of autonomous electric vehicles on power distribution network operation considering dynamic distribution network reconfiguration, travel behaviors, and existence of renewable energy. Access Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at IISE 2019</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2019_1_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/iise2019_1_talk/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Guo will have two presentations at IISE Annual Conference 2019 in Orlando, FL. He will present his work on Competitive Intermediate Facility Location Problems under Traffic Equilibrium on May. 19, 2019, and his work on Interdependence between Transportation and Power Systems, beyond Electric Vehicles on May. 20, 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New funded project on vehicle-to-infrastructure (V2I) planning and safety impacts</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/utc_funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/utc_funding/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at USF CUTR seminar</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/usf_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/usf_talk/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Guo will present his work on a stochastic general equilibrium approach on market-based facility infrastructure development on Mar. 22, 2019 at USF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New funded project on ride-sharing system analysis, sponsored by Argonne National Lab, Department of Energy</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/argonne_funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/argonne_funding/</guid>
      <description>INSPIRE Lab is awarded a project (funding source US DOE) on &amp;ldquo;Impacts of Electrified Ride-sharing on Transportation and Energy Systems&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New publication</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/ep2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/ep2018/</guid>
      <description>New publication in resale vaule of PEVs on Energy Policy based on large scale online true market value data. Access Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finalists in poster competition</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2018_poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2018_poster/</guid>
      <description>INSPIRE LAB&amp;rsquo;s poster on Distribution Network Reconfiguration with Decentralized Autonomous Electric Vehicles was in the finalist (top 6) of the poster competition at the 2018 INFORMS Annual Meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation at INFORMS 2018</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2018_talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 17:54:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/post/informs2018_talk/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Guo will present his work, collaborating with Sandia National Labs and UC Davis, on evolvement of charging infrastructure in a competitive and stochastic market at INFORMs 2018 in Phoenix.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>