<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>graduate-researcher on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</title>
    <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/tags/graduate-researcher/</link>
    <description>Recent content in graduate-researcher on INSPIRE Lab @ UCF</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/tags/graduate-researcher/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Md Nafees Fuad Rafi</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_nafees_fuad_rafi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_nafees_fuad_rafi/</guid>
      <description>Md. Nafees Fuad Rafi is a Ph.D. student of Civil Engineering with a focus on Transportation Systems Engineering at the University of Central Florida. Before joining UCF, he worked as a faculty member at AUST, Dhaka, Bangladesh. He has completed his B.Sc. in Civil Engineering at Khulna University of Engineering &amp;amp; Technology (KUET), Khulna, Bangladesh. His research interest includes Travel Behavior Modeling, Smart Mobility, Data Analytics etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MohamadReza GhorbanaliZadegan</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/mohammadreza_ghorbanalizadegan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/mohammadreza_ghorbanalizadegan/</guid>
      <description>MohammadReza is a PhD student in Civil Engineering (focus: Transportation Systems Engineering) at the University of Central Florida. He earned his undergraduate from Islamic Azad University and master&amp;rsquo;s from Sharif University of Technology, both in Industrial Engineering. He has a strong background in Operations Research, Mathematical Formulation, and Optimization. Mohammadreza&amp;rsquo;s research interests revolve around the application of mathematical and computational tools to address real-world problems in fields like transportation and logistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nima Rashgi Shishvan</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/nima_rashgi_shishvan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/nima_rashgi_shishvan/</guid>
      <description>Nima earned his undergraduate degree in Civil Engineering from the University of Tehran, followed by a master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Civil Engineering with a specialization in Transportation Engineering and Planning from Sharif University of Technology. Currently, he is pursuing his doctoral studies at UCF. His primary research focuses on the utilization of information and communication technologies in transportation, as well as freight transportation and logistics, and the development of sustainable transportation systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saman Mazaheri Khameneh</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/saman_mazaheri_khameneh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/saman_mazaheri_khameneh/</guid>
      <description>Saman is a PhD student in Civil Engineering (focus: Transportation Systems Engineering) at the University of Central Florida. She earned both her BS.c and MS.c degrees from University of Tabriz majored in Electrical Engineering. . She has a strong background in power systems, and her research interests revolve around intersection of power systems and transportation systems. She is currently working on the application of optimization tools in transporation related to electric vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fatima Afifah</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/fatima_afifah/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/fatima_afifah/</guid>
      <description>Prior to joining UCF, Fatima worked as an educator for two years. She completed her undergraduate and master’s degree in Civil Engineering from Bangladesh University of Engineering &amp;amp; Technology (BUET). While studying in BUET, she focused on issues related to child road safety and car-following behavior in heterogeneous road traffic condition. Fatima has succeeded on extracting the vehicle trajectory of heterogeneous traffic stream using image processing which she further used on her master’s thesis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Md Rakibul Alam</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_rakibul_alam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/md_rakibul_alam/</guid>
      <description>Rakibul Alam is a PhD student in Civil Engineering (focus: Transportation Systems Engineering) at University of Central Florida. He completed his undergraduate from Bangladesh University of Engineering and Technology and master&amp;rsquo;s from Memorial University of Newfoundland, both in Civil Engineering. His past research works relate with environmental impact from road pavement maintenance, and pavement life cycle assessment using data science. He served at the faculty of Civil Engineering at University of Information Technology and Sciences (UITS), as an educator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sina Baghali</title>
      <link>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/sina_baghali/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zhaomiaoguo.github.io/people/sina_baghali/</guid>
      <description>Sina got his undergraduate degree from the University of Tabriz and his master&amp;rsquo;s degree from K. N. Toosi University of Technology both majored in Electrical Engineering. Before joining UCF, his research include modeling power systems in optimization problems and modeling renewable energy resources based on data analytics. He is currently a P.h.D student at UCF working on the interdependencies of power and transportation systems in terms of resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>